There. Beautiful.
Thank you.
Are you two really being lovebirds,
or is this just an act?
We agreed to stay married.
Get all those trees out of here.
I don't like them.
Neen, Neen!
Please listen to me!
Stop bullshitting me! Stop it!
- Stop it!
- Neen, that's enough!
Then you can stay with her all you want.
No matter how hard it is,
I won't let go of her hand.
You're together almost all the time,
yet she still found a way to surprise you.
Ms. Runch is awesome.
She was here?
Yes. She just left.
Wait, you didn't see each other?
Runch!
Neen.
I was just stopping by quietly.
You didn't have to come out here.
Take your flowers.
You think a bouquet of flowers
can fix everything?
Yes, Mom?
I'm not at the office yet.
I'll call you when I get there.
Bye.
Second attempt.
What can I get you?
I'd like these three, please.
Sure.
Can I earn M points here?
Yes. You may scan your receipt
on the M Card app
to earn M points.
- Can I scan to pay?
- Sure.
Dessert, from Ms. Runch.
They're all yours, Ms. Nat.
Flowers, from Ms. Runch.
Please get them out of here.
- Chocolate, from...
- I know.
Please get that out of here.
MOM
For this matter,
I'd like to change our whole plan.
Please turn over to page…
Excuse me, Ms. Runch. Your mother called.
Please excuse me.
Yes, Mom? Is something wrong?
Nothing, honey.
I'm perfectly fine.
I was just wondering
if you've had lunch yet.
Mom, I'm in a meeting.
I'm sorry, honey.
I really didn't know.
MOM
Yes, Mom?
Have you left the office yet, Runch?
Not yet, Mom. I'm still finishing my work.
Did you eat yet?
Do you want me to bring you food?
I'm not hungry yet.
Remember to eat. And did you
take the vitamins I sent you?
You need to take them, honey.
Okay, Mom.
I should get back to work now.
I care about you, honey.
I know.
Mom.
Oh, Runch.
You're home.
I fell asleep for a bit.
Mom…
Why didn't you go to bed in your room?
Why'd you wait for me?
I was worried about you.
I called, but you wouldn't answer.
I got anxious, so I sat here and waited
so that I'd see you when you got home.
You know,
you don't have to call me
all the time, Mom.
I have work to do.
Sometimes I really can't
answer your calls.
I understand.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
I'm just happy
to be alone together with you like this.
Whatever you do,
wherever you are, or whether you're tired,
I want to know it all.
And I care about you.
Plus,
it's been a while since we had
our mother-daughter bonding time.
Since you got married,
this is the first time
you've been this close to me.
I didn't mean to stay away from you.
I know.
I'm not upset.
I just missed you.
You should go to bed.
I know.
So should you, Mom.
- Sure.
- Let's both go to bed.
My ring!
Hello, Mom.
Yes, honey?
Could you check in the bathroom for me?
I remember taking off my ring
and putting it by the sink.
I forgot to wear it today.
I checked. I didn't see a ring.
You didn't?
Are you sure?
I could swear I put it by the sink, though.
I'm very sure. I looked all over.
There was no ring.
How strange.
But I swear I left it by the sink.
Don't worry, honey.
Maybe you put it somewhere else.
I'll help you find it.
I'll search all over the place again.
If I find it, I'll let you know right away.
Where on earth is it?
It's not here.
What? The bag's replaced?
Runch.
Runch, where are you going?
Runch!
What are you doing?
I'm looking for my ring.
I told you,
I didn't find a ring in the bathroom.
You don't believe me?
I distinctly remember
putting it by the sink, Mom.
Hey, will you stop it!
Stop looking already! It's dirty!
It's just a ring. What's the big deal?
It's not just a ring.
It's my wedding ring with Neen.
It means a lot to me.
I have to find it, no matter what.
If it's not here, that means it's gone.
What do you mean by that?
What I mean is
some things shouldn't be kept
if it pains everyone in the house.
Why would you say that?
Don't tell me…
You threw away my ring.
Well, it was right in front of me.
And it made me feel uncomfortable.
I'm asking you,
you threw away my ring, didn't you?
Where did you throw it away to?
Uh, Runch...
Answer me!
Answer me, Mom!
Runch, that hurts! Let me go, will you?
So that ring matters more than me?
Where is the ring, Mom?
Mothers will do anything,
especially one
who's as protective as yours.
She'd do it just so she wouldn't
lose you to someone else.
I think you fell for your mother's trick.
Mom.
Please go home.
Are you mad at me?
I'm not.
But you're crossing the line.
Runch, I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through.
What I did was wrong.
Please don't kick me out.
I have no one else to turn to.
I want to stay with you.
That's all I ask.
Runch! No!
It's me, it's me!
Why were you following me?
You scared me!
My eyes are burning.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. It's just.
I didn't want you to walk away,
so I followed you quietly.
I didn't think you'd spray me
right in the face.
I'm sorry for scaring you.
But actually,
I need your help with something.
What do you need my help for?
I want us to team up
and get my mom to show her true colors.
Am I hearing this right?
Yes.
You heard me right.
But I probably
can't handle this alone.
If you want my mom to go home,
we have to work together.
What are you doing?
Mom, you're back!
Did you miss me, Mom?
You're speechless.
That means you did miss me.
Mom, I'm back.
I've come back to stay here,
and I'm not going anywhere this time.
I'll make sure you see my face every day.
- But...
- Let's get along
so Runch can rest easy, Mom.
From now on, I will listen to you.
I'll never ever go against you.
I love you, Mom.
I love you so much.
Did you miss me, Mom?
Gosh, I missed you so bad.
I promise I won't leave you again, Mom.
That brat!
What do I need to do to get rid of you?
What should I do now?
Would you all like
to join us for dinner
at my daughter's tomorrow?
Thank you.
I was thinking
I'd invite my friends
to join us for dinner here today.
Could you take care of it, Neen?
I want a full course meal,
and I want you
in charge of the whole meal.
This evening?
I'm not sure if I can prepare it in time.
There's not nearly enough time.
You'll have to figure it out.
I already invited them.
Neen,
please do this for my mom.
Don't disappoint her.
Okay.
Neen,
you've been on your phone all day.
You didn't get the place ready
or anything.
Yes, Mom.
So will you finish everything in time?
I'm not sure.
Well, what if you don't?
You'll embarrass me.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
I'll try my best.
You'd better hurry up, then.
I don't want it to turn out bad.
Sure, Mom.
You can come out now.
Girls, I'm sorry
on behalf of my daughter-in-law.
She couldn't get everything ready in time.
It's just how rich kids are.
Normally,
her maid does everything for her,
so when I leave her in charge,
she can't do it.
Please don't get mad at her.
You brat.
This time, I'll win.
The appetizer's good, isn't it?
- Oh, yes, it is!
- Wait until you try the entrée.
It's so good.
- Really?
- Of course!
I can't wait.
I hope you all like it.
The presentation's so mouth-watering.
- True.
- Thank you so much.
Can't wait to eat it.
The food's so good, isn't it?
Yeah. All the dishes look so good.
Oh, Ging!
Come join us!
Mom.
- Come on.
- Come sit with us.
- It looks so good, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Oh, I can't wait.
You know, Ging,
I've got to hand it to them.
Neen and Runch are so sweet.
They really took great care of us.
Yeah.
She's so polite and caring.
And everything looks well-prepared.
Mom,
Neen's prepared
a fine dining meal for you.
It's from a famous restaurant in Bangkok.
Luckily, my parents love this restaurant,
so they sent their chefs over just for us.
Normally, they don't do off-site catering.
- Wow!
Your daughter-in-law sure has connections.
Oh, come on.
She's really something.
She's both talented and sophisticated.
That's right.
Ging, can you host a party
like this again someday?
We'll come, no matter how far away we are.
That's right! I loved it.
I was really impressed today.
Let's do this again.
I'm so happy to have you over.
I'll invite you again someday.
- Sure.
- Sounds good.
See, we're both full and happy.
- Thank you for coming.
- Aw.
- Let's meet again soon.
- Sure.
- We'll get going now.
- Okay.
Drive safe.
- If you'll excuse me.
- Sure.
- We'll come again.
- See you, Ging.
- Take care.
Bye.
Good job, Neen.
I'm proud of you.
So where's my reward?
I'll give you one tonight.
Hey, can't you see
your mother's standing here?
Anyway, I need to use the bathroom.
You did it to embarrass me, didn't you?
That was never my idea, Mom.
I just want what's best for you...
Drop the act already.
I really doubt
someone like you could change.
Why are you laughing?
Couldn't keep up the act,
so you finally snapped?
This was your plan, wasn't it?
What are you talking about?
I'm an innocent girl.
I'd never scheme against you.
You're so full of it!
You're just a rude little brat.
You think you're smart?
Don't think I can't see through you.
I'll make Runch hate you so much
that she'll never want
to see your face again.
- Help me, Runch! Help!
- You're crazy!
No! Runch!
- Runch! Runch!
- Crazy bitch! Let go!
- Help me, Runch!
- You're crazy!
Help me! Help!
Runch! Runch! Runch!
- Runch, help!
- Enough.
Stop it!
- Stop it!
- Runch!
Runch,
Neen hurt me, Runch.
Crazy bitch!
That's enough, Mom.
I'm calling Dad so he can take you home.
Why?
Watch this.
I'll make Runch hate you so much
that she'll never want
to see your face again.
Help me, Runch!
- You installed a security camera…
- You're crazy!
- …to spy on me?
- Help me! Help!
Yes.
I did it the day you threw away my ring.
Please let me explain, Runch.
- No.
- Please?
I saw everything.
I saw what you did.
I can't let you stay here anymore.
You planned this, didn't you, Peeracha?
Didn't you, Peeracha?
That's enough. Mom!
Stop it!
Don't you lay a finger on Neen.
Don't hurt her.
I did it all by myself.
Runch…
You should pack your things.
I'm calling Dad so he can take you home.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Your mom's gone home already?
I know it must be difficult for you.
If you want to talk or vent,
I'm always here to listen.
Getting to hug you
and having some peace and quiet
is enough to cheer me up.
Then I'll hug you tighter.
I think we've been too stressed out lately.
Can you take me on a trip?
I want to be with you like this all day
and just do nothing.
Won't you get bored if we do this all day?
Of course I won't.
Just seeing your face makes me happy.
Me too.
What are you doing?
I'm building a house.
A house just for the two of us.
It's all gone!
That's alright.
We can build a new one.
This time, I'll help you build it.
Fine.
Come on.
Hello.
Yes, I'm Gingkamol, Runchlaphat's mother.
A show?
A show, you say?
You're almost there.
Just a little longer.
In five, four, three, one.
Here we are.
Are you ready?
Yes.
‪Ta-da!
And this is
where we're staying tonight.
- Yay!
You're the sweetest!
- You like it?
- Thank you.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
Wow.
Are you hungry?
Hold tight a little longer.
It's almost ready.
Can I help you with anything?
No.
Just sit tight.
Because today,
you're my princess.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes.
Hey. Stop. Stop it.
I told you,
you're my princess today.
Don't do anything by yourself.
I'll do it for you.
Okay.
Here it comes.
The shrimp is so sweet.
I bet it's because you grilled it for me.
- Want some more?
- Yeah.
Can you pour me another?
Neen.
The bottle's empty.
Empty. Gone.
But I want another.
You should stop.
We're out. No, no, no. You're drunk.
Will you still love me if I'm drunk?
I will.
Drunk or not, I'll love you either way.
I'm so glad.
- Huh?
- Then let's go.
Wait... Where are you going, Neen?
Let's dance.
But there's no music.
We don't need a song.
We'll dance to the song in here.
My song?
In here.
Your song too?
And then you grab my waist.
Like so. Right.
And right.
We should stop.
You're drunk, Neen.
And if you don't stop,
I won't be able to stop myself.
Then don't.
No.
Remember,
you're my princess tonight.
I'll do everything for you.
Thank you so much
for taking the time
to be on our show today.
It's my pleasure.
As long as it benefits society.
Actually, our show, Real Talk With Moms
is meant to be a space
where parents can voice
their true feelings,
especially about sexual diversity.
We want the public to see
that not every family can easily accept it.
But trying to understand it
is already an important first step.
I think so too.
Matters like this aren't easy for mothers.
That's right. We wanted to invite you
because you're
one of the mothers who accepted
your daughter's same-sex marriage,
which not everyone can do.
I may not understand it all,
but I love my daughter.
And that should be enough.
That's exactly the idea
we're trying to convey.
The questions we ask
aren't intended to attack anyone.
We just want to tell each story
through a mother's lens.
What she had to go through
before she could accept the truth.
There's nothing to worry about.
Just say whatever you feel.
Say it from your heart.
We believe the viewers
will see that you only want
what's best for your daughter.
Then, I'll say how I really feel.
- Sure.
- So everyone
will understand a mother's love.
Yes.
Ma'am, we'll start in five minutes.
Okay.
Lately, people have been talking
about your dear daughter's relationship.
How do you feel about this?
I, um.
I do admit
that it's not something I expected.
But in the end,
no matter what path you choose in life,
I'll always love you just the same, honey.
I'm just…
Worried about you.
Many people see
your daughter's love
as the courage to be herself.
Do you agree?
I don't believe it's wrong to be yourself.
But sometimes,
the people in your life
may fail to consider all the consequences,
especially for your family.
So you don't approve
of her current relationship?
I don't want to say I don't approve it.
I just want you to have an easy life,
where you don't have to go
against the public opinion,
where you don't have
to sacrifice anything for anyone's love.
Rumor has it
that you and Ms. Peeracha
fight quite often.
Is that true?
I've never had a fight with anyone.
I'm just straightforward.
And I just
want to protect my daughter, is all.
If one day,
your daughter has to choose between
family and love,
what do you want her to choose?
I don't want her to have to choose.
But if love
makes you turn against your family,
I have no choice but to leave you alone…
And hope that one day
you'll understand how a mother feels.
If Ms. Peeracha watches this show,
do you have something to tell her?
I was never angry
or hateful toward anyone.
I just want her to know that
loving someone
shouldn't come at the cost of breaking…
A mother's heart.
1 YEAR AGO
Over the two years we've been together,
we've been through a lot, haven't we?
Just seeing your face
makes me feel like
everything will get easier.
If we ever feel tired,
can I stay by your side just like this?
Of course.
No matter when,
my arms will always be open for you.
Then, do you promise
that we'll always be each other's home?
I promise.
I won't let go now.
Are you ready?
- Yes.
Are you ready, Ms. Peeracha?
- Okay.
What do you like about Ms. Runchlaphat?
I'll keep it short.
Runch is someone who makes me feel
like I don't have to try to be anyone.
Normally, I'm the type
to overthink and imagine things,
wondering if I'm good enough.
But when I'm with her,
she makes me feel like.
I don't have to be capable or strong,
and I don't have to feel okay all the time.
As long as I'm me,
she'll always be by my side.
Plus,
Runch is the type of person who,
even if the whole world was against me,
would always be there for me
without asking questions.
It just feels so secure
to have someone
who you can take a rest with,
cry with,
and dream of a future with.
There.
If you asked me what I like about her,
that would be my answer.
Wait.
That was so long.
That wasn't short at all.
Was it too long?
If it were me,
of course I'd choose my mother.
Your words
made the whole country see it that way.
- See what?
- That Neen's the one who took me
away from you.
If you choose to keep this up,
I'll have to decide.
Runch, Runch!
From now on, no matter what we face,
we won't let go of each other's hands.
I feel so lucky
to have you by my side.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya